[{"answer": "They're every four minutes and last 55 seconds", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Swiss quartz, ha, ha", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'll get it", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I got i", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I want a baby", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Get up. Come on. Let's get some coffee", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You know what the that place problem is? They let the players run the team", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, it is", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, that is so not true", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It isn't", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, it is", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It is", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It isn't", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Isn't", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Breathe", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Breathe", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Breathe", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Breathe", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Breathe", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Breathe", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Breathe", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Breathe", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I got it", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I got it! Hey, you get to sleep with her, I get the cramps", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, you started it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "How, how is this my fault", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah? Well, there's a lot of things my friend never did before I came along", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No, honey, they're not, but don't worry, because we are going to find them, and until we do, we are all here for you, ok", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Ok", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Ok", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Ok", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No, this is a loaner", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I wasn't by myself. I had a doctor, a nurse, and a helper guy.  So, did you see who won the game", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "The woman I love is having a baby today. I've been waiting for this just as much as you have", "docId": "123birth.htm.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You get to be the baby's father. Everyone knows who you are. Who am I? There's Mother's Day, there's Father's Day, there's no... Lesbian Lover Day", "qsentId": 36}]